《黑吃黑》第三季 第三集
Banshee S03E03
你说你留在女妖镇是为了我
You told me you stayed in Banshee because of me.
我是想确保你没事
I had to make sure you were okay.
我有事
I'm not.
听着
Hey, listen.
被枪指着你好像一点都不惊讶
You don't seem surprised to have a gun in your face.
这说明你一直都过的小心谨慎
That's a symptom of a life spent looking over your shoulder.
你是谁
Who are you?
我是特别探员罗伯特·菲利普斯
I'm Special Agent Robert Phillips,
联邦调查局内部调查组
FBI Internal Investigations.
我都不知道联调局里还有内务
I didn't realize the FBI had internal affairs.
那是因为你不是真正的警察
That's because you're not really a cop.
不过我们有大把的时间好好聊
But we'll have plenty of time to talk about all that later.
先去穿好衣服
Why don't you get dressed?
很久以前
There was a time
是我站在床边凝视你的睡颜
when I was the one who would watch you sleep.
你曾是个漂亮的孩子
You were such a beautiful child
前途一片光明
with so much promise.
我从来没想让你失望  母亲
It was never my intention to disappoint you, Mother.
凯
Oh, Kai.
我不会对你失望的
You could never disappoint me.
我只是希望我能相信
I just wish I could believe
你得到了满足
you were content.
谁还会爱你呢  凯
Who will love you, Kai?
你还会爱谁呢
Who will you love?
普罗科特先生
Mr. Proctor?
我  我只是想确认你没事
I-- I just wanted to make sure you're okay.
你要保证  我离开之后
Promise me after I am gone...
你会让丽贝卡搬出去
that you will move Rebecca out of this house.
这不合适  这不健康
It's not proper. It's not healthy.
你保证
Promise me.
我不该扔下她的
I should never have left her.
我不该把她扔在农场里
I should never have left her on the farm
和我父亲一起
with my father.
没事的
It's okay.
她需要我  这些年来  她需要...
She needed me. All those years, she needed...
她现在仍需要你
She still needs you.
而你就在她身边
And you're here for her.
你好
Hi there.
知道吗
You know,
听说通过家里的样子
they say a man's home is
就能了解主人的内心
a window into his mind.
是  我听过
Yeah, I've heard that.
格洛克17
Glock 17.
9毫米口径
9 mil.
真的吗
Really?
对
Yeah.
是我的得力助手
Gets the job done.
你应该了解我的几件事
You should know some things about me.
我的上司要求结果
My superiors demand results,
但他们并不关心是怎么得来的
but they're not in the least concerned how I achieve them.
所以如果我是你
So if I were you,
我会加强警觉
I would exercise some caution.
如果我是你  也一样
And if I were you, I'd do the same.
同意
Agreed.
那就戴上吧
Why don't you put those on?
你就是普罗科特的看门恶犬
So you're Proctor's big bad watchdog.
在我看来  你也没有多凶
You don't look so tough from where I'm standing.
计划是这样的
So here's the plan.
首先  我会杀了你
First, I'm gonna kill you.
然后我要进去慢慢折磨死你老板
Then I'm going inside and I'm gonna slowly gut your boss
和他那《草原小屋》里的侄女
and his "Little House on the Prairie" niece.
我不这么想
I don't think so.
诺拉
Nola.
让我死
Let me die.
你已经死了
You already did.
是重生的时候了
It's time to start living again.
数据回收器是什么玩意
What the hell is a data skimmer?
物如其名
Exactly what it sounds like.
它会扫描并储存从编码智能卡得来的元数据
It scans and saves metadata from encoded smart cards.
我们从他们那窃取真实身份信息
We stealing real IDs from them
然后我就能给我们做假的了
so I can make fake IDs for us.
早这么说不就完了
That's all you had to say.
费那劲干嘛  现在干嘛
That wasn't so hard, now, was it?
天知道这事从不简单
Lord knows it ain't ever easy.
这个给你  现在要让你
This one's yours. Now, I want you to--
测试
Testing!
好用
It works.
努力点  别给我搞砸了
Do your best not to fuck this up.
斯特林工业
这周都三次了
That is the third time this week.
他们这是要干嘛
You think they're trying to tell me something?
我需要六个身份信息
I need six IDs.
数的时候别动嘴
Try not to move your lips while you're counting.
好了  我该去取下来了
Okay, I got to grab it.
不行  还差三个
Mm-mmm, three more.
没时间了
Running out of time.
还差一个
One more.
我的一串钥匙
Oh, I had some keys--
原来在这
Oh, there they are.
-还差一个  -谢谢
- One more. - Thank you.
够了  出来吧
I got it. Get your ass out.
我有个很重要的商谈
I got a big business meeting
钥匙丢了就去不了了
and I can't get nowhere without these keys, you know?
太感谢了
Thank you so much.
咋了
What?
既然我们不用过大厅
If we were never going past the lobby,
你干嘛让我穿一身西装
why you got me wearing this damn suit?
因为没有休闲星期一的说法
'Cause there ain't no such thing as sweatpants Monday.
开车啊
You can drive.
我喜欢经典摇滚
You know, I prefer classic rock,
但是乡村音乐
but something about country music
让人身心舒畅  不觉得吗
that soothes the soul, don't you think?
你怎么找到我的
How did you find me?
我在局里有一项专门的工作
You know, I have a rather specialized job at the Bureau.
我是个问题处理者
I'm a fixer of sorts,
我调查死亡及失踪的探员
so I investigate dead and missing agents.
当然  失踪的那些基本上也都死了
Of course, the missing ones almost always turn out to be dead, too.
比如吉姆·拉辛
Like Jim Racine?
然而我在纽约州北部的
Instead I found his body
一间旧农舍外面找到了他的尸体
outside an old farmhouse in upstate New York.
是吗
Really?
他尸体的一部分吧
Well, what was left of him.
罗伯特·菲利普斯探员
他被烧得很惨
He was burned up pretty bad.
杀了他的混蛋却没事
But not the slug that killed him.
九毫米口径格洛克
Glock 9 mil?
不是
No.
点308口径步枪
.308 rifle round.
挺有意思啊
Isn't that interesting?
他手里那份
Not as interesting as the
关于你的厚厚的档案才更有趣
inch-thick file that he was keeping on you.
原来纽约市警察局的
You know, it turns out that the NYPD's
匿名钻石大盗
John Doe Capital Diamond thief
竟然是宾夕法尼亚州
turned out to be the new sheriff
女妖镇的新警长
of Banshee, Pennsylvania?
太跳跃了
That's quite a leap.
大概吧  但这件事越发有趣了
Maybe, but the story gets better.
尤其是在教堂
Especially the part about the church,
火拼那部分
the gunfight.
要超级有种
I mean, it takes some king-sized balls
才敢用那种方式干掉兔子吧
to take on a guy like Rabbit in a way like that.
当我想到前科犯冒充警长时
And when I think about an ex-con posing as a sheriff,
我想也许这两个有种的家伙是同一人
well, I think maybe those are the same big balls.
我受宠若惊
Well, I'm flattered,
但你只是在浪费时间
but you're wasting your time.
你很了解浪费时间这回事  对吧
You know something about wasted time, don't you?
我不理解  我是说
I don't get it. I mean,
你出来后随便去哪儿都行
you could have gone anywhere when you got out.
比如去天堂岛  在黑沙滩上
You could have found a black sand beach somewhere in paradise,
找个淡棕色美女夜夜笙歌
a new golden brown senorita every night of the week.
天哪  要我我就这么干
My God, that's what I would have done.
但你偏不  你跑来了女妖镇
Oh, not you. No. You came to Banshee.
你在偷走你十五年光阴的
You played dress-up right down the road
女人家街头玩起了变装
from the woman who stole 15 years of your life.
她一定很惹火
She must be something.
不然就是你内心深处
Or else there's something inside of you
还想被惩罚
that still wants to be punished.
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我觉得你话太多
I think you talk too much.
我第三任前妻也是这么说的
That's what my third ex-wife told me.
好了  出来
Okay, get out.
你要放我走
You're letting me go?
不  我放你出来撒尿
No, I'm letting you take a piss.
回市里还有很长一段路
It's a long way back to the city.
中途不会再停车了
We're not gonna stop another time.
-我不用  -我没问你  出来
- I'm good. - I'm not asking. Move.
-敢乱来的话  -知道  你就开枪
- And if you try anything-- - Yeah, you'll shoot me.
-我懂的  -对  出来
- I get it. - Yeah. Come on.
厕所
你知道吗
Hey, you know what?
客用厕所
-我改变主意了  -怎么说
- I think I changed my mind. - How's that?
我不想回纽约
Well, I don't think I want to go back to New York.
说得好像你有的选一样
You make it sound like you have a choice.
选择总会有的
Well, there's always a choice.
我想举报一起抢劫案
I want to report a robbery in progress
在钻石仓库
at the Capital Diamond warehouse.
锯木厂河畔路211号
211 Saw Mill River Road.
纽约警署财产
禁止复制
我是朱利亚斯·邦纳警探
I'm Detective Julias Bonner.
今晚是我的人把你们扣下的
It was my team that took you down tonight.
恭喜
Congratulations.
你很聪明  应该知道
You are smart enough to know
纽约警署财产
禁止复制
设圈套的人是你的老板
that whoever you're working for set you up.
可以吗
May I?
要喝点什么吗
May I offer you something to drink while you wait?
咖啡  茶
Coffee? Tea?
还是浓烈些的
Something stronger?
在我看来  你已经知道
The way I see it, you know you got jail
我们已经没有谈话的必要了
on the other side of this conversation.
纽约警署财产
禁止复制
你已经很多年没有回家了
You aren't going home for many years.
该清醒了  混蛋
Time to wake up, asshole.
他醒了
There he is.
抱歉让你等这么久
Sorry to keep you waiting.
但愿我的手下让你有宾至如归的感觉
Hopefully my associates have made you feel at home.
如你所见  对于我这种体型的人
As you can see, comfort is a priority
舒适是最重要的
for a man of my dimensions.
适当的旅游是必要的
Some travel is unavoidable,
但轿车  货车  飞机
but cars, vans, planes,
对我来说都是一种侮辱
they all present indignities for me.
你可以试着偶尔吃点沙拉
Well, you could try eating a salad now and then.
我认为肥胖的玩笑不该存在于我们之间
I think fat jokes are beneath us both.
这很难说
Well, that's hard to say
鉴于我不知道你他妈到底是谁
seeing as I have no idea who the fuck you are.
我的名字
My name
是雷蒙德·沃尔顿·布兰特利
is Raymond Walton Brantley.
布兰特利
Brantley, that's the guy
你就是偷了他的钱  对吗
you stole the money off, right?
听着  我看到了不该看到的东西
Look, I saw some shit I wasn't supposed to see.
布兰特利是个偏执的疯子
Brantley, Brantley is a paranoid fuck.
是吗
Yes?
不是
No?
也许
Maybe?
对于你我唯一确定的
The only thing I know for sure about you
是你不是谁
is who you are not.
你不是卢卡斯·胡德
And you are not Lucas Hood.
对吗
Isn't that right?
没关系
It's okay.
除了之前的一顿暴打
Despite a particularly nasty beating,
联调局老鼠小组的菲利普斯探员
Agent Phillips here of the FBI's rat squad
一直安静地像只老鼠
remained as quiet as a mouse.
杰森·胡德在哪
Where is Jason Hood?
我不知道那是谁
I have no idea who that is.
-真的吗  -是的
- Really? - Yes.
不是
No.
也许
Maybe.
我...他死了
I, just, he's dead.
他死了
He's dead.
他死
He's de--
把杰森·胡德交给我
Give me Jason Hood
然后菲利普斯探员
and Agent Phillips
再也不会找你的麻烦
will never cause you discomfort again.
说实话
To tell you the truth,
我从没担心过菲利普斯探员的事
I've never really been worried about Agent Phillips.
所以你要是还摸得到自己的屌
So if you can find your dick in there,
干嘛不滚回去自己打飞机
why don't you go fuck yourself?
如果我是你  我会稍微考虑一下
If I were you, I'd take a moment to consider how tenuous
你有什么讨价还价的余地
your bargaining position truly is.
也许你的女孩
Maybe you got a girl...
独自在黑暗中等待  想知道发生了什么
alone in the dark waiting and wondering what happened.
我说过应该让我去普罗科特家
I told you I should have handled Proctor's house.
你的机会马上就来了
You'll get your chance soon enough.
你一直这么说
That's what you keep saying.
让我去打他的七寸
Let me hit him where it hurts.
让普罗科特知道我们才是老大
Show Proctor that we're in control.
你还没准备好
You're not ready.
别让我再提醒你
Don't make me tell you again.
切顿
Chayton.
你们先出去
You guys take a walk.
汤米
Hey, Tommy.
高中后我从没这样过
I haven't been out this way since high school.
你本不该来这
You should not have come here.
你为什么偷那些枪  切顿
Why'd you steal those guns, Chayton?
如果我不知道实情
If I didn't know any better,
我会说你是在训练军队
I'd say you were training an army.
不过那就太疯狂了  不是吗
But that would be crazy, right?
疯狂
Crazy.
疯狂是让居留地
Crazy is allowing the reservation
变得和外界一样腐朽堕落
to become as corrupt as the outside world.
-有多少  -不过朗西德
- How many-- - But that's just what Longshadow
和乔治·亨特已经这么做了
and George Hunter have done.
他们说我们是歹徒  是黑帮
They call us outlaws, gangbangers.
说得好像我们才是问题所在
Treat us like we're the problem.
那是因为你把暴力当做解决办法
Because you treat violence like it's the solution.
为了防止家园落入普罗科特这种人手中
I will do anything to protect our land
我愿意做任何事
from men like Proctor.
你所做的只是在伤害自己人而已
All you're doing is hurting more of our own.
这比任何一个人都重要
This is bigger than any one person.
你去跟死在普罗科特泳池里的那个红骨帮说吧
Tell that to the dead Redbone they pulled out of Proctor's pool.
或者躺在重症监护室的那个
Or the other one in the ICU.
正义之战总有伤亡
Casualties of a righteous war.
我们还是孩子的时候
You know, when we were kids
你和汤米搬来和我们住
and you and Tommy came to live with us...
你那么害羞
you were so shy.
那么温柔
So gentle.
我跟所有人说你是我亲哥哥
I told everybody you were my real brother
因为我希望那是真的
because I wanted it to be true.
现在我都快认不出你了
Now I barely recognize you.
库珀·杜鲁门运输
你还挺经打的
You sure can take a hell of a beating.
彼此彼此
I'll give you that.
你为什么不说实话呢
Why don't you just tell him the truth?
-他知道你在撒谎  -他什么都不知道
- He knows you're lying. - He doesn't know shit.
-他以为我在撒谎  -有什么区别呢
- He thinks I'm lying. - What's the difference?
菲利普斯探员  这可是最基本的心理战术
Come on, Agent Phillips, that's basic psy-ops protocol.
要想扳倒敌人物理上的优势
The only way to overcome a physical advantage
-就要建立心理上的优势  -心理上的优势
- is to establish a psychological one. - A psychological one.
没错  记起来了
There you go. You remember.
在匡提科上那节课时我睡过了
Yeah, I slept through that class at Quantico.
你没有
No, you didn't.
你可以玩你喜欢的心理游戏
You know, you can play all the mind games you want,
但我们不可能活着离开这里
but we're not leaving here alive.
你心里清楚  对吧
You know that, right?
要我说  待在这里
Way I see it, I'm better off in here
也比困在你车里好
than I was in the back of your car.
如果这是真的  你得扪心自问一下
Well, if that's really true, you have to ask yourself
你的三观有多么扭曲
just how fucked up your universe really is.
我早就想过了
The thought has crossed my mind.
这些年来  我也击碎过不少
You know, I have cracked
扭曲的心灵  而你
some pretty twisted minds in my time, but you--
你不想放过我  是吗
You're not gonna give up on me, are you?
绝不
Not a chance.
说到哪了
Where were we?
你刚刚问我有关杰森·胡德的事
You just asked me about Jason Hood.
你让我滚回去自己打飞机
And you told me to go fuck myself.
我们都被绑起来了
We're all caught up.
我他妈会杀了你
I'm gonna fucking kill you.
艾米莉  是我  我打来问个好
Hey, Emily, it's me. Just checking in.
总之  回我电话  好吗
Anyway, call me back, all right?
-一切还好吧  -好得不能再好了
- Is everything okay? - Couldn't be better.
我要下班了
I'm, I'm clocking out.
有胡德的消息吗
Any word from Hood?
没有  什么都没有
Nope. Nothing.
也许我们该把他的办公室改成游戏室
I'm thinking we should turn his office into a game room.
你说呢
What do you think?
我其实有点担心他
I'm actually pretty worried.
我试着联系他一整天了
I've been trying to reach him all day.
真的吗
Really?
反正你的工作也跑不了
Well, your paperwork's not going anywhere.
不如去他家看看情况
Why don't you head over to his place and see what's what?
-真的吗  -真的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
-谢谢  布罗克  -不用谢
- Thanks, Brock. - Sure.
找到他了告诉我一声
Let me know when you find him.
-没问题  -好
- All right. - All right.
-你要走了吗  -是啊
- You heading out? - Yep.
要去什么好地方吗
Anywhere good?
只是和老朋友一起喝杯酒而已
No, just having an afternoon drink with an old friend.
普莱特恩恩  我在想什么
Platinumm, what the hell was I thinking?
抱歉
Sorry.
跟热辣前妻搞上
You know, there is worse things
也不是世界末日
than getting some from your hot ex-wife.
我知道
No, I know.
她总是反复无常  你不了解艾米莉
There's always a flip side with her. You don't know Emily.
我只知道  没人逼你跟她上床
I know there's nobody forcing you to bump uglies with her.
这点没错  说得太对了
That is true. That is very true.
不过  事情没那么简单
But, you know, it's, it's complicated.
男人总会把老二插进
Ugh, how come every time a guy goes sticking his dick
不该插的地方  这很复杂吗
someplace he shouldn't, it's complicated?
-我只是  -别说了
- Well, I just... - No.
有时候当我...
You know, sometimes when I...
你的前妻很清楚自己在干什么
Your ex knows exactly what she's doing.
她把你训的服服帖帖
She's got you exactly where she wants you.
上了床就不知道自己是谁了
Losing your fucking mind over some bomb-ass pussy.
我明白  我明白  我明白
I know. I know. I know.
你是明白怎么做
You already know what to do,
但你不会付诸行动
but you're not gonna do it.
你是个聪明的女人  普莱特恩
You're a wise woman, Platinumm.
住手  白痴
Hey, shithead!
杀了他  你们就什么都问不到了
You kill him, you'll never get what you want.
菲利普斯探员说得对
Agent Phillips is right.
要不要告诉我他在哪
Are you gonna tell me where he is?
让他出去透透气
Give him some fresh air!
下午好  副警长
Afternoon, Deputy.
来点什么吗
Can I get you something?
不了  谢谢  你看见警长了吗
No, thanks. Have you seen the sheriff?
他今天没来上班
He missed his shift today.
没有  没看见
No. No, I haven't.
不过他总会出现的  一向如此
But he'll turn up. He always does.
你很了解他吧
You know him pretty well, huh?
我对你也是这样
I could say the same about you.
-是吗  -是的
- Could you? - Mm.
恐怕不是吧
I'm not so sure.
有一些人  在你了解他之前
Some people, you can know them
就清楚他的为人
before you know about them.
或许吧
Maybe.
如果喝着啤酒听这些  可能觉得更深奥
Or maybe that'd sound a lot more profound if I had had a few beers.
是  我也觉得
Yeah, I don't doubt that.
好了  有消息告诉我
All right, well, if you hear from him...
一定
Will do.
现在不说就没机会了  神秘先生
Now or never, mystery man.
-杰森·胡德在哪  -他死了
- Where is Jason Hood? - He's dead!
他妈的他死了  我说过了
He's fucking dead. I told you.
我为什么要信你
And why should I believe you?
因为是我杀的  满意吗
'Cause I killed him, all right?
给你30秒
30 seconds.
要是哪一个字我不信  你就等着被碾死
I doubt a word, you become roadkill.
他给我5万
The kid offered me 50 grand
让我杀了你派来的拉风男
to take out your man in the fancy suit, all right?
先付了2万5  事成之后再付剩下的
25 up front, 25 when it was done.
你杀了昆汀
You killed Quentin?
是费了点力气
Well, it took some doing...
确实是我杀的
but, yeah.
继续说
Go on.
在我杀了昆汀之后
So after I killed Quentin,
杰森  他不想付剩下的钱
Jason, he didn't want to pay up
所以威胁要揭发我
and he threatened to expose me.
那你为了拿钱把他杀了
So you killed him and took the money?
做事拿钱
Fair is fair.
我的钱现在在哪
Where is my money now?
在女妖镇
It's back in Banshee.
-所有的  -是的
- All of it? - Yes.
杰森·胡德
总共加起来到底有多少钱
And exactly how much is all of it?
布兰特利  他喜欢低调的处理这种事情
Brantley, he likes to deal with this sort of thing up close and personal.
6万2千
62,000.
我会送你回家的
I will take you back home.
你带我去看杰森·胡德的尸体
You will show me Jason Hood's body.
把我的钱还给我
You will return my money.
你刚才为什么
What's going to stop you from
没一枪崩了我
shooting me the moment I do?
因为你不在名单上
You're not on the list.
看样子在我拿回钱之后
Seems I will be taking a trip south of the border
要去南部边境转转了
after I retrieve my money.
很遗憾  菲利普斯探员
Sadly, Agent Phillips,
我们不能一同前往了
your home is not on the itinerary.
万达  告诉科尔先生到前面靠边停
Wanda, tell Mr. Cole up front to pull over.
我的朋友们会陪同你
My associates will escort you
去你下一个目的地
to your next destination.
我们要去哪
Where the hell is that?
很安全的  菲利普斯探员
Safe travels, Agent Phillips.
走吧
Let's go.
万达  让科尔带我们回女妖镇
Wanda, tell Mr. Cole to take us back to Banshee.
他们随后就到
The boys will catch up later.
然后给我调杯喝的
And mix me a drink.
经典布雷顿  多加糖
Bulleit Old Fashioned, extra sugar.
马上就来  布兰特利先生
Right away, Mr. Brantley.
六十九英里
你要回去蹲监狱了
You're going back into a cell.
纽约警署财产 不得复制
你会被判八到十年牢
You're facing eight to ten years.
你这一生完了
Life as you know it is over.
站住
Hey!
别挡道
Get out of the way!
趴下
Stay down.
-回来  -趴下
- Get back! - Down.
去看看后面的房间  确保没人出去
Check the back rooms. Make sure everyone's out.
雷文  我是布罗克
Raven, hey, it's Brock.
听着  萨沃伊脱衣舞俱乐部发生人质劫持
Look, I've got a 211 in progress at the Savoy.
目测有五名袭击者
Looks like five assailants
和大概二十四名平民被困在里面  快来
and possibly two dozen civilians trapped inside. Hurry.
起来
Get up.
妈的
Fuck.
真正的猎犬  昆汀
True gundog, Quentin.
总能成功让敌人现型
He could flush out the best of them.
跟我讲讲  你是怎么打败他的
Tell me, how'd you beat him?
不  我什么都不会说
No, I'm not telling you anything.
除非你先告诉我你们为什么为了
Not until you tell me why you came so far
杰森·胡德这样的混蛋大老远来
for an asshole like Jason Hood.
像你这样的人肯定不会为了6万块
I mean, a guy like you doesn't come all the way
横跨整个国家而来
across the country for 60 grand.
我这种人为了5毛钱都会来的
A guy like me would come across the country for 50 cents.
开始挖吧
Start digging.
我的身体已经坏了
My body has failed me.
也许是我自找的
I failed it. Either way.
结果  简单的事情我都做不来
Things that you take for granted, I can't do.
去杂货店买东西
Simple trip to buy groceries
或者去饭店吃饭
or have a meal at a restaurant.
连女人都上不了
I can't even fuck anymore.
但我有自己的分类账本
But one thing I do have is my ledger.
我自己记账
I keep my own books
来保持收支平衡
and I keep everything balanced.
一个小数点都不会差
Not a decimal point out of place.
罪恶都在账本的细节里
The devil is in the details.
而这些细节
And the details
是像我这样的人唯一所有的
are all that a guy like me has.
如果是这样的话  我猜你很想知道
In that case, I bet you'd love to know
杰森·胡德最后说了什么
what Jason Hood's last words were.
告诉我他说了什么
Tell me what he said.
他说要告诉你
He said to tell you...
他很快就会见到你的
he'll see your fat ass real fucking soon.
上来  你  给我出来  出来
Up here now. You, outta here! Get outta here!
快走
Move!
现在趴下
Down now!
待在这里
Stay here.
你要干嘛
What are you doing?
不要
No!
你自己喝吧
You have it.
科尔要来了
Mr. Cole.
-万达  猎枪放在哪里了  -柜橱里  底层右面
- Wanda, where are the shotgun shells? - Cabinet, bottom right.
-看别处  不要看我  -不
- Look away. Don't look at me. - No.
所有人听着  听着
Everyone listen up. Listen up.
我们不是来杀你们的
We're not here to kill you.
但完事以后
But when I'm done here... -
你们都要重新换份工作了
...you're all gonna have to find new jobs.
扔掉你们的武器  把手举起来
Drop your weapons! Hands in the air!
不要  你他妈别想了
Don't! Don't you fucking do it.
都不许动
Nobody move.
我说了把你们的武器扔掉  伙计们
I said to drop your weapons, fellas.
小子  那把刀要是再靠近她的脖子
Son, that knife gets any closer to her neck,
我就把你的头打爆
I'm gonna blow your fuckin' head off.
万达
Wanda.
警察
Sheriff's Department!
马上把枪放下
Put down your guns right now.
汤米  汤米  我是比利·雷文
Tommy! Tommy, it's Billy Raven.
你和你手下马上投降
You and your boys need to surrender now
不会再有人受伤
and no one else gets hurt.
除了你以外  条子
No one except for you, cop.
妈的  汤米  你要听我的话
Damn it, Tommy! You need to listen to me.
不
No!
阿尔玛  萨沃伊这里需要经济医疗救护
Alma, we need EMTs at the Savoy now.
我去查看后面的房间
I'll clear the back rooms.
-别乱动  -去死吧
- Stay still. - Fuck you!
别他妈乱动
No, thanks. Don't fucking move.
-雷文  你那边没事吧  -没事
- Raven, you okay over there? - Yeah.
刀
Knife!
胡德死哪去了
Where the fuck is Hood?
69公里
西
69英里
够深了
That's deep enough.
转身
Turn around.
你不想这样的
You don't want to do this.
杀联邦探员会给你找大麻烦的
Killing a federal agent will get you the needle.
再见
Good-bye.
我没有杀拉辛
I didn't kill Racine.
我知道
I know.
那你他妈的来这干嘛
So what the fuck are you doing here?
因为好奇
I was curious.
我被派寻找失踪探员
I was tasked to find a missing agent.
你跟这事无关
You're not part of that story.
调查局对你一无所知
The Bureau doesn't know anything about you.
那我干嘛不把你埋这儿呢
So what's stopping me from leaving you in this hole?
自救这门功课你学的太垃圾了
You're doing a pretty shitty job of saving yourself.
看来我们俩都得用功了
Seems we both need to work on that.
同意
Agreed.
我们没事了
So we're good?
对
Yeah.
没事了
We're good.
但你应该知道...
But you should know...
在我以为你会是那个
I had to do something to cover my ass
你不是的人时  我不得不做了些
when I thought you would turn out to be
自保的事
who you weren't.
你干了什么
What did you do?
房间  7
纽约警局所有  勿复制
女妖镇警局  调度员
美国司法部
联邦调查局
机密
抱歉
Sorry.
我们都不知道你叫什么
We don't even know what to call you.
怎么了
What is it?
什么
What?
他们的[荷兰语]
Godverdomme!
女妖镇边界
你的生活  那个生活
Your life, that life,
结束了
is over.
-我自己干的  -你不是
- I work alone. - No, you don't.
楼里有人和你一起
You had someone in that building with you.
你们两个在从楼顶下落时
And you two weren't performing some remote hack
黑掉了市场上一些最先进的保安系统
on some of the most advanced security systems on the market
让我查查
while rappelling from the roof,
这就有三个人了
so by my count, that adds up to three guys
还不算兔子先生
not counting Mr. Rabbit.
什么  你以为我在为什么犯罪首脑工作
What, do you think I work for some criminal mastermind
他还自称什么兔子先生吗
that goes around calling himself Mr. Rabbit?
没错  我就是这么认为的
Yes, I do. Yes, I do!
交出兔子
Give me Rabbit.
把他供出来  我跟你谈个交易
Give him to me and I'll cut you a deal.
也许你会被判18个月  但一年就可以出狱
Maybe you get 18 months. You'll be out after a year.
我会给你提供证人保护计划
I would offer you witness protection,
但你不会有身份
but you don't have an identity,
所以我猜你大概不需要新身份
so my guess is that you won't need a new one.
你到底是谁
Who the hell are you?
在我看来
The way I see it,
你知道谈话的另一个方向是进监狱
you know you got jail on the other side of this conversation.
我用你的指纹提取了档案
I used your prints to pull your file.
压根没有  我们甚至不知道你叫什么
There isn't one. We don't even know what to call you.
你是个幽灵  你所知道生活已经结束了
You're a ghost. Life as you know it is over.
之后的很多年  你都回不了家
You aren't going home for many years.
你会被关回监狱  而明天的这个时候
You're going back into a cell and tomorrow at this time,
你会在莱克斯等审判
you'll be in Rikers awaiting trial.
快点吧  这案子不断牵扯到兔子
Come on, this case has Rabbit written all over it.
什么  你以为我在为什么犯罪首脑工作
What, do you think I work for some criminal mastermind
他还自称什么兔子先生吗
that goes around calling himself Mr. Rabbit?
交出兔子
Give me Rabbit.
把他供出来  我跟你谈个交易
Give him to me and I'll cut you a deal.
好
Okay.
为了记录在案  说出你的名字
This is for the record. State your name.
约翰·史密斯
John Smith.
你在干嘛  耍我吗
What are you doing? Are you fucking with me?
没有  是你在耍我
No, you're fucking with me.
交易是真的
The deal is real.
你说你想接受交易  你这个傻逼
You said you wanted to take the deal, you stupid motherfucker.
也许  但我不会坐在这
Maybe, but I'm not gonna sit here
替你干活
and do your fuckin' job for you.
这是你的葬礼  混球
It's your funeral, asshole.